Paul Buddle | Software Developer

Location: Nottingham Telephone: 07718626195 Email: paul-buddle@hotmail.co.uk

Professional Profile

I am an enthusiastic programmer aiming to get my first job in the industry. I have recently completed Harvard's online computer science course, where I learnt to write clean and efficient code whilst responding to technical and functional specifications.

I am competent with Python, Javascript, SQL and C, as well as a variety of frameworks, dependency management tools and Git version control. I am becoming familiar with Agile work processes and I am currently teaching myself to build .NET applications in C#.

Having worked as an AV technician for many years I have developed excellent troubleshooting abilities as well as strong communication skills, especially when discussing technical subjects.

I am now looking to move into a more intellectually stimulating work environment and am ready to continue my coding development as part of a team.

Core Skills

- Python, C, Javascript, SQL
- HTML. CSS. Bootstrap
- React, Flask
- Git version control

- Independent
- Fast and capable learner
- · Problem solving/troubleshooting
- Technical experience

Work Experience

Nottingham Contemporary (2013 – present)

Nottingham Contemporary is a public art gallery and events venue. Since starting there in 2013 I have progressed through several roles in the organisation; Gallery Assistant, Events Technician, and FOH.

Events Technician (Nottingham Contemporary 2014 – present)

- Responsible for sound, projections, IT and lighting for a variety of events such as gigs, theatre productions, lectures, panel discussions and film screenings.
- Roles include liaising with external clients, providing them with technical solutions and solving problems.
- Working with other departments, coherently communicating technical subjects

- Responsible for training staff in use of AV equipment.
- Working independently, often under pressure.
- Use of visual coding software MAX.

FOH/Night Officer (Nottingham Contemporary 2018 - present)

- Front of house duties such as customer service in the gallery shop.
- Cashing up and closing the building.
- Duty manager for large scale events, such as club nights and gigs.
- First Aid and Fire training (Updated 2022)
- Responsible for the safety of staff and the public.

Gallery Assistant (Nottingham Contemporary 2013 - 2018)

Education

Freecodecamp – online coding bootcamp modules (2022 - present)

Harvard University CS50x: Introduction to Computer Science (2021)

- Final project in web development
- Languages learnt included C, Python, Javascript, SQL, HTML and CSS.
- Topics included abstraction, algorithms, data structures, resource management, security, software engineering, and web programming, through a variety of problem solving exercises.

Nottingham University Fine Art BA (Hons): 2.1 (2013)

Bradford College BTEC Art Foundation Diploma: Distinction (2010)

Guiseley School A Levels: 3 (A-C) (2009)

Guiseley School GCSEs: 11 (A-C) (2007) including A in Maths and English

Hobbies

- Composer, musician and music producer
- Experimental music algorithmic/generative compositions
- Building electro-acoustic instruments